hardcoreware.net 2003-06-22

# hardCOREware.net - What makes us tick?

|   
|   
---  
  
**About hardCOREware.net - NO BS**

We are a hardware gaming review site.  We review the latest, greatest (and lamest, on occasion) hardware and games, and tell you about it.  We tell you **nothing** less than the **blatant and total truth**.  If something kicks ass, believe me, you will be the first to know.  The same goes if something sucks ass.

What makes us different from other hardware gaming sites? Well, the fact that we give you the straight, **no BS** story on hardware.  We're not going to slam every piece we review, but we aren't going to be like other sites who have nothing bad to say about anything, just so they can score free hardware.

We will have several reviews each week.  The hardware will range from the latest graphics cards and CPUs, right down to cases, fans, heatsinks, and mice.  Everything that is important to you, the hardcore gamer.

**hardCOREware is:**

---  
  
**Staff**

**Carl Nelson (lowlight) - Editor in Chief**[lowlight@hardcoreware.net](mailto:lowlight@hardcoreware.net)

Carl Nelson (lowlight) has been a hardcore gamer from the get-go.  From copying code out of magazines and into his Vic-20 at the age of 5, to starting (and running, of course) several gaming web sites, he has seen just about everything.

Other sites include: [Surreal-News.com](http://www.surreal-news.com/) \- A site devoted to bringing you the latest news regarding Surreal Software, and ALL their titles.  Right now this includes a series of games for the **Lord of the Rings** franchise.  You will find the most extensive database of player-created levels on Surreal-News, as well as the official DevBoard, where YOU suggest to Surreal what YOU want to see in games.

 **lowlight's Favorites:**

 **Now Playing** (updated 08.30.02) **:**  
Jedi Knight II - Jedi Outcast  
Battlefield: 1942  
America's Army  
Ultima Online  
Outcast (the sleeper classic from 1999)

 **Music:  
**Almost any House Music or Eurodance  
Funker Vogt  
Daft Punk (All-time favourite)  
Brooklyn Bounce  
Frontline Assembly  
Noise Unit  
Skinny Puppy  
NIN  
Front 242  
Rob Zombie  
Classic EBM ROM files :)  
Almost anything from the Baroque Period (Bach of course, but also Pachelbel, Handel, Purcell, etc)

 **Movies:** (In no particular order) **  
** Princess Mononoke  
Once Upon a Time in China I, II, & III **  
** Star Wars  
Se7en  
The Green Mile  
Forrest Gump  
Trainspotting  
Saving Private Ryan  
The Blair Witch Project  
Fight Club  
Braveheart  
Three Kings  
Jurassic Park  
Memento  
Crouching Tiger, Hidden Dragon  
Being John Malkovich  
Spirited Away  
Iron Monkey

 **Directors:** (In order)  
P.T. Anderson  
David Fincher  
Yuen Wo-Ping  
Steven Spielberg  
Tim Burton  
James Cameron

 **Actors:** (In no order)  
Don Cheadle  
Brad Pitt  
John C. Reilly  
Samuel L. Jackson  
Mark Wahlberg  
Morgan Freeman  
William H. Macy  
Phillip Seymour Hoffman  
Tom Hanks  
Edward Norton  
Jet Li  
Donnie Yen  

---  
  
**Bryan Pizzuti** **\- Senior Editor** [ bpizzuti@hardcoreware.net](mailto:bpizzuti@hardcoreware.net)

Despite the fact the Bryan is an IBM employee, we still consider him to be hardcore :)

Name: Bryan Pizzuti  
Date of Birth: April 1st, 1975  
Location: Poughkeepsie, NY  
Marital Status: Single  
Ocupation: Network Support

**Hobbies** :  
PC tweaking  
Linux tweaking  
Recycling old PCs into something functional  
Praying for broadband  
Collecting board games  
Reading  
Cooking  
Being a geek  
Being PROUD of being a geek!  
Praying for broadband some more

**Currently installed games** :  
Anachronox  
Pac Man: The New Adventures  
Jagged Alliance 2  
Fallout Tactics  
Star Trek Voyager: Elite Force  
Conquest: Frontier Wars  
Jane's USAF  
Tachyon: The Fringe  
3D Ultra Cool Pool  
Uplink  
Empire Earth

**Current book collections** :  
The Frank Herbert "Dune" series  
Harry Turtledove's "WorldWar" and "Colonization" series  
The "Starfist" series  
The Brian Herbert "Dune, House ____" series  
Orson Scott Card's "Ender" series

**Current rig (Brag Section)** :

AMD Athlon-C 1.2 GHz  
256 MB PC-133 SDRAM  
ECS K7S5A w/ on board LAN  
Hercules 3D Prophet 4500 Kyro2 64 MB  
TurtleBeach SantaCruz Sound  
Toshiba 12x DVD (IDE)  
Sanyo 12/10/32 BurnProof/RAW CDRW (IDE)  
WD 7200 RPM 15 GB HDD (IDE)  
WD 5400 RPM 20 GB HDD (IDE)  
Apple 20 inch Trinitron monitor  
Logitech MouseMan Optical  
Creative WebCam GO  
Logitech PageScan USB  
US Robotics PerformancePro 56k modem (pitiful, huh?)  
Some keyboard or another.

**Computer experience** : Been working with PCs and video games since they were invented.   

---  
  
**Privacy Statement**

**Information Collection and Use**   
hardCOREware is the sole owner of the information collected on this site. We will not sell this information to others in ways different from what is disclosed in this statement. hardCOREware collects information from our users at several different points on our website.

**Cookies**  
A cookie is a piece of data stored on the user’s hard drive containing information about the user. Usage of a cookie is in no way linked to any personally identifiable information while on our site. 

Some of our business partners use cookies on our site (for example, advertisers). However, we have no access to or control over these cookies.

**Log Files**  
We use IP addresses to analyze trends, administer the site, track user’s movement, and gather broad demographic information for aggregate use. IP addresses are not linked to personally identifiable information. 

**Links**  
This web site contains links to other sites. Please be aware that we [hardCOREware] are not responsible for the privacy practices of such other sites. We encourage our users to be aware when they leave our site and to read the privacy statements of each and every web site that collects personally identifiable information. This privacy statement applies solely to information collected by this Web site. 

**Newsletter**  
Readers may join our newsletter by using the form at the top of the page. By joining the newsletter, you may receive solicited advertisements from hardCOREware directly.  **Your email address will never be sold or lent to another party for advertising purposes** , solicited or otherwise.  Everyone who joins our forum is automatically subscribed to the HCW Newsletter.  You may still participate in the forum even if you unsubscribe.

**Notification of Changes**  
If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on our Homepage so our users are always aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under circumstances, if any, we disclose it. If at any point we decide to use personally identifiable information in a manner different from that stated at the time it was collected, we will notify users by way of an email. Users will have a choice as to whether or not we use their information in this different manner. We will use information in accordance with the privacy policy under which the information was collected.  

**No Fear**  
[06.21.03] @ 10:57 AM   
Thanks for voting on my case guys! **mfox**  
[06.20.03] @ 10:49 AM   
mmm golf + naked chicks.... **Leo**  
[06.20.03] @ 10:32 AM   
OMG,it's the best looking case ever **El Nutsio**  
[06.20.03] @ 5:34 AM   
my lasagna is burning **Mick**  
[06.20.03] @ 3:44 AM   
Some guys have all the luck and there there's me **borna**  
[06.19.03] @ 1:00 PM   
t dizzle, lets not forget canoli **rstarr**  
[06.19.03] @ 3:16 AM   
2 hardCORE mods on the main page! **mfox**  
[06.18.03] @ 8:46 PM   
wow, big shocker there
